When everybody leaves you lonely
And times are worse than sad
And the world is falling on your head
Just remember, for all you know
Good or bad, come what may
You're gonna live tomorrow
If you don't die today
It takes a muscle to fall in love
Now the fear got in me...?
Your mother said you were having a hard time.
Yeah, I... I just broke up with my girlfriend.
We went out from the end of high school till... well, through college.
What did she do?
She studied Marketing at school. She's got a job at an ad agency now.
And you?
Me? I... I studied Neuroscience...
with a primary focus on the relationship between the eye and the brain.
My thesis project was about peripheral vision.
It dealt with something called 'crowding' and 'size pooling'.
How the width of one object
is given a weighted average of the objects around it.
The effect is called 'size pooling'.
- It was published, actually. - That's great.
I'm not sure I understand, but it's great you were published.
Yeah, that's OK, nobody does.
How long were you together?
For almost 5 years.
I moved in with her right after graduation.
Things were...
Well, they were nice for a while,
but then she wasn't happy anymore... or I wasn't making her happy.
She didn't like what she was doing.
I tried to be supportive, encourage her not to settle. But then...
I'm living at home now.
Excuse me. I'm not feeling so well. I'm still feeling jetlagged.
Do you understand "jetlagged?"
Yeah. Don't worry.
Do you still speak to each other?
No. Not really.
The way that it ended...
She started coming home late from work...
and one night she got into bed with me
and I moved to hold her, and I just...
smelled this smell on her.
What do you mean?
I'm sorry. Maybe it's a little inappropriate.
No. Go ahead.
I...
I just smelled this guy on her.
She smelled like sex.
Like sweat and latex.
And this guy, whoever he was, was all over her.
I mean, she denied it, of course,
but it was clear.
I don't know, maybe I overreacted.
Well, whatever. She's a whore.
I'd like to meet somebody new.
Hello?
OK, thanks, I'll be right down.
My cab is downstairs.
- Can I help you with your bags? - No. Thank you.
So, you know where everything is.
Just change the sheets at the end...
make sure the heater is off and the kitchen is clean.
Yeah... yeah. And how long will you be away?
I'm going to the south. So maybe a week, maybe a month.
I don't know, it depends.
But you'll be here for a week? Or much longer?
No. Just a week. I have to figure out where I'm going to next.
Oh, right.
Leave the key under the mat outside.
I'm sorry I have to leave just when you arrive.
That's OK. Don't worry.
- Have a safe trip. - Thank you.
- Give my love to your mom. - I will... I will.
- Goodbye. - Ciao.
If the walls were too thin, you would...?
'Hey, Chelle belle...
"Dear Michelle..."
'Hey, Michelle... How are you?
'How's everything?
'I know you said not to contact you.
'I know, the last time we spoke, we agreed not to contact each other.
'But I'm in Paris now, about to start traveling around for a few months.
'And since we always spoke about coming here together,
'I just thought I'd let you know. Things are great.
'So far, things are great.
'I'm spending time with our cousin Carlo and his friends.
'I... I met someone, actually.
'I wanted to tell you I'd met someone.
'I'm meeting some interesting people here and practicing my French.
'I miss you.
'I hope you're well and maybe we can speak soon?
'Maybe we can speak soon...
'Love...
'Yours... sincerely.
'Sincerely, Si.'
Cunt!
There was a time...?
Heaven has reached down to earth.
And what does this tell us?
That God has not forsaken us.
That He is always watching over us.
That He loves us.
Through this sign, He has manifested His presence.
He is telling us.
You are not alone.
Excuse me.
Excuse me... Could I have a light, please?
Yeah.
Thanks, you're very nice.
- OK? - Yeah.
Yeah, thanks.
- Are you taking the Métro? - Of course.
Do you...?
- Do you both live in Paris, or not? - We actually live nearby.
I'm sorry but... What did you say?
We live right around here... in this neighborhood.
Yes, OK, I understand.
Me, I stay here for a few days but...
then I leave soon for...
I'm going...
In fact, I leave...
East, maybe...
I'm sorry about my French. It's awful, I know.
It's OK, don't worry.
- What's your name? - What?
- What? - Your name?
Got a problem?
What?
Don't you say excuse me?
He's not French...
No, I...
I'm sorry, sir.
So he doesn't speak French?
OK. So I'm apologize man.
- OK... - OK?
No regret.
OK, yeah. I'm sorry.
You have tiny hands, man. Like a girl.
OK...
And why do you have two girls and I have none?
OK, that's it, enough.
- Look, man, I'm sorry... - Hold on!
Why did you hide these sweethearts?
- Please let go of me, sir! - Are you laughing at me?
No! I am not fucking laughing at you!
Damn it!
- Sorry. - No, it's OK.
Do you know what time it is?
It's 10:05.
We don't have time?
Not much. No.
I'm hungry.
It was nice meeting you guys.
- Bye. - Bye.
- See you around, maybe? - Nice meeting you.
Do you like natural woman?
Fuck me...
I'm very horny.
Please write me what you like.
Can you hear me now?
Fuck...
Fuck me in the ass Fuck me in my ass.
Oh, yeah...
Fuck me, babe.
So hot ass for you.
Yeah...
Fuck me in the face.
Fuck me in the face. Fuck my face.
Fuck me...
Fuck me... Fuck... Fuck me...
Fuck me bad... Fuck me...
Fuck me...
Did you come?
Yeah? Did you come?
Come back for me, love.
You are welcome, buddy.
Thank you, too.
'Hi, Michelle.
'I haven't heard back from you in a while.
'Not sure if you're getting my emails or if you're ignoring me.
'I just wanted to see how you were. You could at least get back to me.
'There's nothing I could possibly do from here.
'I'm sending you my best. Simon.'
Evening, sir. Excuse me, good evening.
You speak English?
- Yeah? - Yeah.
One minute... Do you wanna see French pussy? Lap dance? Strip club?
- No, that's OK, thanks. - Come on, my buddy...
My friend...
Wanna spend the evening with some pretty girls?
What?
A nice night with pretty girls. Interested?
Right over there.
What do you mean exactly?
You go in, have a drink, look around...
There are pretty girls to keep you company.
And if you want more, if you want sex, that's possible too, OK?
How much is it?
10 Euros for a drink...
If you don't like it, you can leave.
What do you think? It's a great souvenir of Paris.
Trust me, I'm not a crook.
Over there?
Good evening.
- Good evening. - Good evening.
- Hi. - What's your name?
My name's Simon.
- Sabrina, nice to meet you. - You too.
Will you have a drink with me?
Yeah, but how much will that be?
- 20 Euros. - 20?
Thank you.
Where are you from?
New York.
- New York City... - Yeah.
I don't speak very well, English.
I present my friend, it's no problem for you?
- OK, sure. - Victoria, come here.
- This is my friend Victoria. - Hi.
Are you all set? No problem?
- Sure. - OK, it's very good.
I go in the bathroom and I come back, OK?
- OK. - Bye.
- Thank you. - You want to go in the back?
- How much is that? - It's free.
We just sit there, and that's all.
- Yeah, OK. - Come on.
You're very handsome.
I'm not saying that just for work, I really think so.
That's sweet. Thank you.
See this girl?
- Sabrina? - The one I was talking to...
This girl, she doesn't need money - she wants money!
Today she got three clients and I only got one.
Normally, it's a trade, you know?
If she has one client, I get the next one...
and she gets the next one, and it's a deal.
I treat her like a sister. If I have food, I share my food with her.
If she's happy, I'm happy for her.
But for her it's not about sharing.
- And me? I need this money. - Yeah, I understand.
So you're visiting Paris?
Yeah. Yeah...
- And you have a girlfriend? - No.
What do you do?
For now? Nothing. I just finished school.
I don't see you very well.
I need to look at you closer.
I have myopia.
Yeah?
I studied eyes in college.
- Really? - Yes.
I studied the relationship between the brain and the eye.
- You speak French very well. - No, that's not true.
- Yes, you do. - I studied in high school, but it's bad.
Do you want to make love?
How much is that?
If you say 150, I say OK.
Some girls say "It's the price" and they won't go down... 200.
With me, I can go down for 150.
- 150...? - Yeah.
I give half to my boss. If I make 50, I give him 25.
OK.
But...
with you, it's not like sleeping with an old fat, ugly man. You know?
With you, I will like it.
I...
I spent all my money at the bar. I only have a credit card.
- You have a credit card? - Yeah.
That's OK. You can give it to me.
OK.
Thank you.
Nadia?
Sorry.
That's OK.
I have a scar.
A scarf?
No, a scar. S-C-A-R... 'scar'.
Here, you know.
- That's OK. - I just prefer to tell you.
I prefer to say it before to people.
How are you feeling?
I feel good.
Can I...
Can I just look at you?
Yes.
- This is the scar. - It's OK.
Can you turn around, please?
Jesus!
Oh, Jesus Christ!
Fuck...
- I'm sorry. - It's OK.
I didn't wanna come.
It's OK. As long as you're happy.
Yeah... I'm happy. I'm happy.
Thank you.
Are you OK?
- And you? - Yeah.
What is that?
It's a fox. My mother gave it to me.
Look.
Here.
- It's a mess. - No... it's OK.
Hold on...
I have to take it off.
It's better off.
Take my number, if you like.
Take my number, so we can see each other outside.
It's the same price, but it's better.
OK.
I miss her.
'I know, honey.
'It's OK now. It's gonna get better.'
Yeah.
'Have you talked to her?
'Si?
'Si, can you look at me?
'Hello? Hello!'
No. I haven't talked to her.
'Well, I don't get that.
'If you still wanna make this work,
'maybe you should call her.'
Hh. I don't know.
Yeah, I guess.
I wasn't good to her.
'That's ridiculous.
'Everything you did for her...
'Look, do you still wanna be with her?'
I don't know.
'Go meet a French girl.
'Meet an Italian girl. Meet somebody.
'Just stop being miserable.
'It's not healthy.'
'Si?'
I'm not your girlfriend, you can say what you want.
Yeah?
OK.
- Say, "Fuck me." - Fuck me.
Say, "Fuck me."
Fuck me.
'Hey, Simon. I'm happy to hear
"'you've been traveling and doing well."
'I've been hesitant to write back to you because the way we left it.
'I thought it would be better for us to take some time apart,
'in every sense of the word.
'I don't know when you're coming back to the city.
'But when you do, please respect me and my space.
The truth is that I don't think I know you, or that I'll ever really know you.
'I don't think you ever knew me.
'I've come to realize that in the past few months.
'I'm happy now.
'The last time we saw each other, you frightened me
'and I don't feel comfortable being around you any more.
'I wish you all the best. Sincerely, Michelle.'
Really? I missed a party?
No, it was great. I had it all to myself.
What, like I don't need cash?
Hi, girls!
- How's it going? - Everybody's here.
Where else would we be?
Want a drag?
Why you staring?
You got a problem?
I was attacked in the street. Can I come in?
Who did this to you?
I was... I was attacked. These kids, they took all my stuff.
Where?
At this train station.
I'm sorry.
What do you want me to do? I'm working now.
I...
You don't have any friends?
No, I...
I just needed some help
and I didn't know where else to go.
Do you think I could just stay with you for a few minutes?
No, not now.
OK...
If you want, we can meet in 2 hours
in the bar called Le Café au Rendezvous.
On the left, at the corner.
It's OK?
Wh-when will you be there?
When I finish work.
In two hours.
OK.
- Are you OK? - Yeah, I'm fine.
So, where do you live?
I... I don't.
You don't know where you live?
No... I was supposed to leave.
- What? - I was supposed to leave tonight.
And now you don't have a place to stay.
No.
Not for now.
OK. So... do you wanna stay at my place?
Is that OK?
- Let's go. Should I pay for this? - Yeah, thanks. Thank you.
Sit over there.
- You have a nice place. - I rent it from an old lady.
She's a bit lonely.
Your parents...
you can't call them for help?
I don't really talk to my parents any more.
But I'll try and figure something out tomorrow.
Thank you.
Fuck... It stings.
- That it? - Yes.
Do you have any other wounds?
I'm sorry, what?
Where...
where else did they hurt you?
I don't know. I'm not... I'm not sure.
Let me see.
What do you want?
I can't sleep.
Could you talk to me for a few minutes?
About what?
I don't know.
Anything.
Is Victoria your real name?
My name is Noura.
- Nora? - Noura...
Noura.
How long have you worked at the bar?
A few months.
What did you do before?
I was working in a supermarket outside Paris.
Is that where you're from?
Yeah.
I lived there until I...
I was divorced.
You were married?
Was it bad?
He was very violent.
He never let me go out.
Once, I woke up in the middle of the night.
I was pregnant.
I had a baby boy inside me.
My belly was so big.
I woke up suddenly...
and there was blood everywhere.
And I walked into the kitchen.
And my husband was there. He looked at me.
I was covered in blood, it was everywhere.
And before going to the hospital...
he fucked me in the kitchen.
Did you understand what I just said?
I think so, yeah. You have a son.
Thanks for being so nice to me.
'Hey, Mom. I'm in Prague and about to head to Sarajevo.
'I'm sorry I've been out of touch, my reception's awful out here.
'I'm feeling better than I have in a long time, so don't worry about me.
'I met somebody, by the way. I think you'd like her.
'She's not a bitch..
'When I get back, I really wanna focus again
'and not be such a pain to you and Dad, moping around the house all the time.
'I feel good being out here and it was worth taking this trip.
'I think you'll be surprised by how focused I am when I get back.
'I love you. Send my best to Dad.
'Love... your fox, Si.'
- Are you there? - Yeah.
- Hey, how are you? - Bad day.
What happened?
I saw a client at a hotel.
Very aggressive.
But he left me some coke.
Want a glass of wine?
Yeah, sure. That'd be nice.
You know...
the night I came into the bar to say goodbye
and I saw you with that other guy?
I know that I shouldn't have felt this way,
but it made me feel really weird.
Does it make you feel weird?
I was working.
Do you think people do what they do just because they like it
and not because they have to?
You know, most of these guys...
If they would get hit by a car, I would not even care.
W-w-what about their wives?
I mean, do you ever think about their wives?
No, I don't think about that.
No...
Well, I mean, think about it for a second, because...
most of these guys, they are probably married, right?
And if their wives knew about you, then...
well, they'd be very upset.
- It would ruin their lives. - Probably.
And take the guy tonight, for instance.
I mean, is he married?
Yeah. He is.
Does he have money?
He does.
OK, I mean, imagine this.
Your phone... it doesn't have a camera.
But, if it did, you'd take this
and you'd put it right here.
Go sit over there.
And whatever happened in that room... you would have it.
And then what?
And then...
And then...?
I mean,
instead of taking a little money
from a lot of men,
you could take a lot of money from one.
And it's so easy to use these guys.
Do you mind if I change the music?
No, go ahead.
It was the one thing they didn't take.
When everybody leaves you lonely
And times are worse than sad
And the world is falling on your head
Just remember, for all you know
Good or bad, come what may
You're gonna live tomorrow
If you don't die today
It takes a muscle to fall in love
Now the fear got in me
Cutting me deep
That's where it's gonna stay
And never leave
Someone come and lay my worry
Someone come and kill...?
I can't sleep.
Are you OK?
I was thinking about these guys.
They have wives.
They have money.
I don't know where they live, but I have their numbers.
OK.
That's OK.
We could figure that out.
I got the phone.
Take a look.
I bought you a shirt.
Thank you.
- Do you like blue? - Yeah... I do.
I love navy blue. It's got class.
It's perfect. Thank you.
Try it, like this.
Hold on! It's not right.
There was a time when my world was filled with darkness
DDDarkness
And I stopped dreaming now I'm supposed to fill it up with something
Something, something
Sorry, excuse me.
Are you Jean?
- Yes. - Did you see a girl tonight?
What?
You have the number for Victoria? Please send her a message with your email.
Why?
We have something to show you.
Well. Let's see it now.
No, I'm sorry. That's not possible.
OK. I'm going to speak in French, do you understand?
Yes, I understand.
I'm a cop.
Cop.
Understand?
Yes.
That means that I could,
if I wanted to...
I can break your fucking head!
Do you understand?
Yes.
If I fuck a whore, what's it to you?
Do you really have something, or are you just fucking with me?
Cause if you do, I'll hurt you.
Understand?
I'm sorry. It's nothing. Forget it.
No!
Stop it.
Stop.
Stop. Want to see what it feels like?
You're such a fucking pain!
Hold on, let me show you.
Turn around.
Do you like that?
- Yeah? - Yeah.
Like that?
OK, come here.
Yeah, that's good.
- Faster? - Yeah...!
Oh, fuck.
Fuck!
Come here.
You OK?
- Yes. And you? - Yeah.
Have I told you about the first time I saw a woman on the Boulevard?
I walked down the Boulevard. My mother held my hand.
We were going to Sacré Coeur. It was a Sunday.
That day...
I noticed a woman leaning against the side of a building.
She was big.
She was wearing a miniskirt, without stockings.
She stared at me.
She was beautiful.
And with her finger, she gave me a sign like this.
She was so close, I could smell her.
At that time, I didn't know what the smell was.
Now, I know.
It was sex.
When I was older I went back to find her,
just to ask her, "What did you want with me?"
You see?
"What did you want to do with an 8-year-old boy?"
Undress.
René?
Yeah.
You have Victoria's number?
Excuse me?
There's something Victoria would like to show you.
Please send her a message with your email.
Why?
So she can send you this video. I could also leave it in your mailbox.
Wait, wait, wait...
René?
You're a kid.
Is this it?
- Do you have the film for me? - No, not now.
It wasn't easy for me to get this money.
I've got a wife, a kid, a home.
- Yeah, I understand. - I have responsibilities.
Yeah. Yeah... This isn't for me. This is for her.
Is this it?
Come on. Don't make a scene. Please.
- I should buy you some shoes. - Yes.
- Are you gonna hop on the Métro? - Why?
I think I'm just gonna walk from here.
- Yes? - Yeah.
- Here? - Yeah. There's a shop close by.
- I'll see you in a few hours... OK? - OK.
- Bye. - Bye, sweetie.
- Bye. - Bye.
Are you sure about how you're feeling?
Look me in the eyes.
So?
Enough said. Want a drink?
Just a coke, please.
You'll come by again...
- I hope so. - You won't forget us?
Of course not.
You're staying in Paris, I hope?
No, no, I'm not leaving.
No, one day at a time.
Love's fleeting.
Whatever it is, I'm much better right now.
Here's to love!
May you find love, too!
Hey!
Do you... remember me?
Yes! Yes, I remember you.
Yeah, Simon. You're...
Marianne.
You live around here?
Yes...
What about you?
- Yeah... - I thought you left Paris.
I was gonna leave, but I liked it so much here
that I decided to stick around for a little while.
And... where are you living?
I'm staying at a hotel nearby.
Look. I'm gonna meet somebody right now, but can I call you?
- Yeah. You want my number? - Yeah.
- Do you have paper? - Yeah.
Look.
This is your fault.
It's you who did this.
What do I do?
- What? - He didn't take the money.
OK.
Can I get you anything?
Here, I have something for you.
When I was a kid
my mom gave me this pin
because she said I reminded her of a little fox.
Me... I always wanted to be a tiger.
Oh, yeah?
I always thought of myself as more of a lion.
And what are you studying?
French Literature.
- Yeah? - Yeah.
OK. What period?
The Middle Ages and the Renaissance.
And what are you studying?
I graduated, earlier this year actually.
But I was studying Neuroscience.
My focus was the relationship between the eye and the brain.
My thesis project was about peripheral vision.
It dealt with something called 'crowding' and 'size pooling'.
How the width of one object is given a weighted average of the objects around it.
It's called 'size pooling'.
Anyway, it's boring, I know.
But it was published, actually.
And what are you doing in Paris?
Honestly?
Yeah.
Absolutely nothing. I...
I came here to do nothing at all for a little while.
OK.
- Do you mind if I ask you something? - No.
I was curious about...
your eyes... how they move like this.
Yeah...
It comes from my father.
And it is called "nystagmus."
- Nystagmus. - Yeah.
OK. I don't know what that would be in English.
Yeah.
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to embarrass you. It's very...
very charming, actually.
Thank you. I'm OK.
I mean it. It's very pretty.
Thank you.
- Simon? - Yeah, it's me.
Where were you?
I went to get us some food.
Why were you gone for so long?
Yeah, I'm... I'm sorry about that.
I went for a walk.
Are you OK?
Listen. Tomorrow, I'm gonna need some money
because I'd like to buy you something.
What are you doing?
Make love to me.
Oh, no, no, no, no...
'René. Leave me a message after the beep.'
Hey, René, it's me again.
Listen. We didn't expect to have to call you again so soon, but...
we need to talk about more money.
I'm just gonna keep calling you until I reach you. And, OK...
Thank you, goodbye.
'René. Leave me a...'
René. Leave me a message after the beep.
René, pick up your fucking phone when I call you.
Walking up to me expecting
Walking up to me expecting words
It happens all the time
Present company accepted
Present company except the worst
It happens every night
Present company excluded in every way
Present company
Makes me wanna stay
Killing it with close inspection
Killing it can only make it worse
It sort of makes it breed
Present company accepting
Presently we all expect the worst
Works just like a need
Present company
Included in the fight
Don't you want me to wake up?
Then give me just a bit of your...?
Could I just look at you?
- Yes. - Yeah?
I don't like this.
- What? - The way you're looking at me.
Why? You're beautiful.
Come here.
- Are you hungry? - Yeah.
- Where should we go? - Montmartre.
Jesus... I'm sorry.
Who is it?
It's just my... my cousin who I've been staying with.
What?
No... I thought you were staying at a hotel.
Yeah, you told me so.
No... I was staying at a hotel when I first arrived. Now I'm staying with my cousin.
But he keeps calling me...
and, in case it's important, I should talk to him.
Can you get the bill, maybe order me another coffee?
- Yeah. - Thank you.
Hey... Everything all right?
'Why didn't you come home last night?'
I... I know.
I'm sorry I stayed out late.
'Who are you with?'
Just a friend.
'What friend?'
Listen. I can't talk right now, but don't worry. I'll be home soon.
- Are you OK? - Yeah, I'm fine.
It's just my parents, they were worried about me.
They kept calling my cousin apparently.
I haven't talked to them in a week.
- But your parents are divorced. - What?
You told me your parents are divorced.
Yeah, they are divorced. I mean, my mother and my biological father.
But my mother remarried. I have a step-dad.
One second.
- Hello, René? - 'No. Who is this?'
- I'm sorry. Who's this? - 'Mathilde.
'Did you call René's phone earlier?'
I... Yes, but can I please speak to René?
'No, you won't be able to speak to René.'
- Excuse me, what did you say? - René's gone.
'Tell me why you were calling René's phone so many times.'
Listen, now's not a good time for me. Can you please have René call me?
Not now, sir!
I'm sorry. This guy... Jesus!
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine. I'm just having a bad day.
It's fun having coffee with you!
What?
I'm just kidding.
- What does that mean? - Nothing! I'm kidding.
Jesus Christ!
You know what, I'm sorry. I...
- If you have to go, go. - I...
I don't have any money. Can I get you back?
Yeah.
I had fun.
OK, I'll call you.
Excuse me.
I got a call
from a woman today.
And I think that we need to leave.
Where were you last night?
Why didn't you come home?
I told you.
I was out.
Listen.
We need to go as soon as possible.
You disgust me.
Did you not hear what I just said? We need to go.
Get the fuck out.
You're a piece of shit.
And you lie.
- I don't understand when you speak French. - You're a liar.
All right.
I'm leaving.
That's right, leave. You're pathetic.
And take your money.
Take it.
I don't need your money.
Look at yourself, look...
You're a coward.
You're not a man.
You know, we get what we deserve.
What the fuck are you talking about?
I did this for you. You could use that money for your son.
I never asked you for anything, Simon.
I was doing just fine as I was.
I called.
What?
You heard me.
You called who?
- What did you do? - I called her!
Oh, you cunt.
You're all fucking cunts.
I love you.
I love you. I do. I love you.
You're crazy.
You're a sick man.
You're sick!
Fucking bitch!
Put your fucking arms down!
Fuck.
- Hey. - Hi.
I'm sorry, I'm freezing.
I was waiting outside for somebody to let me in.
- I'm sorry about earlier. - That's OK.
Are you OK?
No, I'm...
I don't feel well.
I'm sorry, I...
I didn't know where else to go. I just wanted to see you.
Do you think I could stay with you guys for just a couple of days?
Would you come in and sit?
I... I'm sorry to interrupt.
It would just be for a couple of days, until I figure out...
where else to go.
Yeah, I'm...
I'm sorry, but I can't help you.
You can't stay here.
- OK... - Sorry...
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday to you...
Happy birthday, Carlo
Happy birthday to you
Thanks guys!
Oh, shit.
Carlo, someone's here to see you.
What are you doing here?
I'm sorry to interrupt, but...
I didn't know anybody would be here. I just came to get my luggage.
- Are you OK? - Yeah, I'm fine.
I met a girl. I was traveling light for a little while.
- That's good. - Yeah.
It's my birthday so I'm having a few friends here...
- Happy birthday. - Thank you.
Let me introduce you. He's the son of my mother's friend.
Sort of my American cousin.
- Hi. - Hi.
You want to drink a glass?
Do you mind if I take a shower?
No... Please do.
Excuse me.
- Have a nice evening. - You, too.
I was putting him up for a while and...
He didn't stay long.
'Your call has been forwarded to an automated voice message system.'
'Hi, you've reached Mary. Please leave a message.'
Mom?
Mom...
Mom!
'Michelle...
'I've spent a lot of time in the past couple of months
'reflecting on myself and our relationship.
'I've never cried as much as I have in that time about anything or anyone.
'I know now that the only way for either one of us to grow, especially me,
'is for us to have time apart.
'I became too nested and reliant on you.
'Emotionally and even financially, in a way -
'something I had never expected, or wanted.
'I know my behavior at times probably only made the atmosphere more toxic.
'I have so much love in my heart to give, and I know the man that I want to become.
'The kind of man that would make my father proud.
'It's not lost on me that for almost 5 years
'I had one of the finest women I've ever known as my partner.
'I had the love of my life, and now I don't and that kills me.'
- No, take the passport out, please. - What?
You take the passport out of the wallet.
OK.
So, what have you been doing in Paris?
I was here on holiday.
And what did you do?
- Excuse me? - What do you do?
- What is your job? - I was a student, but I graduated.
And what do you study?
French Literature.
You know that you stayed more than 90 days.
No, I...
I'm sorry. I didn't realize.
Hold on.
'Whatever happened before, I'm not dangerous.
'I'd never hurt you.
'I know I need this time to grow and put my life in order.
'And I know you needed this time, too.
'I hope we can meet soon,
'as the people we know and...
'I hope we can meet soon, as the people we know...
'I hope we can meet soon
'as the people we know we can and will become,
'on the corner of 12th and University,
'we'll kiss where we first kissed and start again.
'I'm sorry, and I'll see you soon.
'Love always. Simon. Your lion.'
OK, it's fine. You can go.
Go on.
Thank you. Goodbye.
华立字幕组原创翻译 双语字幕 华立字幕组期待你的加入
翻译：小笨钟     后期：lovelzy残天
When everybody leaves you lonely
And times are worse than sad
And the world is falling
on your head
Just remember, for all you know
Good or bad, come what may
You're gonna live tomorrow
If you don't die today
It takes a muscle to fall in love
It takes a muscle
to fall in love
It takes a muscle to fall in love
Now the fear got in me...?
你母亲说你现在正处于困难期
是的, 我...我和女朋友分手了.
我们从高中结束的时候开始...直到大学结束.
她做什么的？
她在学校学市场管理.她在广告代理业找到了分工作.
你呢?
我? 我...我是学神经系统科学的...
研究眼睛和大脑的关系的.
我的论文项目是间接视力.
它是通过 'crowding'和 'size pooling'来处理的.
一个物体有多宽
是由周围物体加权平均决定的.
这种效应称为 'size pooling'.
- 实际上，它被出版了.- 很好啊.
我不确定我明白,但很高兴你的论文被出版了。
是的，这很好, 没什么人会知道。
你们在一起多久了?
大约5年了.
毕业后我和她一起住.
事情...
开始的时候还好,
不久之后，她就不再高兴了...或者说我没去让她高兴.
她不喜欢她现在做的.
我尝试去支持她,鼓励她去解决. 但是之后...
我现在住在家里了.
打扰一下.我现在感觉不太好.还在倒时差.
你明白"时差?"
是的. 不用担心.
你们现在还可以聊天吗?
不.
我们结束的方式...
她开始下班晚回家...
一天晚上，她和我一起睡
我去抱她,然后我...
在她身上闻到到那种味道.
什么意思?
不好意思.这可能有点不恰当.
不会，继续.
我...
我闻到这些东西.
她闻起来像性爱.
像汗水还有乳胶.
然后这些家伙, 无论他是谁,都是上了她.
我的意思是, 她否认了,
但是这很明显.
我不知道, 可能是我反应过度了.
无论怎样，她是个婊子.
我想去认识些新的人.
你好?
OK,谢谢了,我马上下去.
我的出租车就在楼下.
- 我需要帮你拿行李吗?- 不用了.
你知道所有的东西在哪了吧.
走之前换一下床单...
确保微波炉关了还有厨房的清洁.
是的... 是的.你会离开多久啊?
我要去南部.所以可能是一个星期，可能是一个月.
不知道，要看情况.
但是你要在这儿呆一个星期吗？或者更长的时间呢?
不. 只是一个星期. 我要确定我要去的下一个地方.
噢，好的.
把钥匙留在外面垫子底下.
我对你刚来到我就要离开感到很抱歉.
没关系.不用担心.
- 旅途安全.- 谢谢.
- 替我问候你妈妈.- 我会的....
- 拜拜.- Ciao.
如果墙壁太薄，你会...... ?
'嘿, Chelle belle...
"亲爱的Michelle..."
'嘿, Michelle... 最近还好吗?
'一切还顺利吗?
'我知道你说过叫我不用联系你.
'我知道，上次我的谈话,我同意不去联系你.
'但是我现在在巴黎, 开始为期几个月的环游旅程.
'我们经常说要一起来这里,
'我只是想让你知道.这里非常棒.
'目前为止,一切都很棒.
'我和我表兄Carlo还有他朋友在一起。
.
'我... 我碰见了一个人, 实际上.
'我想告诉你我遇见了一个人.
'我在这里遇见了一些有趣的人，还有在练习我的法语.
'我想你了.
'希望你一切都好,然后也许我们很快就可以说话了?
'也许我们很快就可以说话了...
'Love...
'Yours... sincerely.
'Sincerely, Si.'
艹!
There was a time...?
天堂已经到达了人间.
这告诉了我们什么?
上帝没有抛弃我们.
他在注视着我们.
他爱我们.
虽然这只是信号,他已经展示出了他的存在.
他在告诉我们.
你不是孤单一人.
抱歉.
不好意思...可以借个火吗?
可以.
谢谢，你们人很好.
- 可以了吗?
- 嗯.
谢谢.
- 你们要去 Métro?- 当然.
你们...?
- 你们都住在巴黎吗?- 实际上我们住在附近.
很抱歉但是...什么?
我们都住在这附近....
好的，我明白了.
我, 我在这里住几天但是...
然后我会去...
会去...
事实上，我会去...
东部，可能...
我对我的法语很抱歉.它很糟糕，我知道.
还可以，不用担心.
- 你叫什么名字?-什么?
- 什么?- 你的名字?
有问题?
什么?
你连道歉都不用说?
他不是法国人...
不，我...
我很抱歉，先生.
他不说法语?
好吧，那我想你道歉吧.
- 好的...- 好的?
不用内疚.
好的，我很抱歉.
你的手很小.就想女人一样.
很好...
为什么你有两个女人，我一个都没有?
你够了.
- 听着，我很抱歉...- 等下!
你为什么要把这些美女藏起来?
- 请松手!- 你在嘲笑我吗?
没有，他妈的我没在嘲笑你!
操!
- 对不起.- 不用，还好.
你知道现在几点吗?
10:05.
我们没时间了
不是很多.
肚子饿了.
很高兴见到你们
- 拜.- 拜.
- 回头见?- 很高兴认识你.
你喜欢正常女人吗?
操我...
我很好色.
写下来你喜欢什么.
你现在可以听到我吗?
操...
操我菊花 ,操我菊花.
噢，Yeah...
操我, 宝贝.
你的菊花太热情了.
Yeah...
给我颜射.
给我颜射.给我颜射.
操我...
操我..操我... 操我...
狠狠地操我... 操我...
操我...
你射了吗?
是的?射了吗?
再找我, 甜心.
不用客气, 伙计.
谢谢.
'你好, Michelle.
'这段时间都没收到你的回信.
我不确定你是没收到邮件还是在忽视我.
我只是想知道你最近怎样了.至少你可以回一下我.
'在这里我没办法做些什么.
'最后的祝福.Simon.'
晚上好, 先生.抱歉, 晚上好.
你会说英语?
- 是吗?- 是的.
一分钟... 你想试一下法国阴道吗？钢管舞? 脱衣舞夜总会?
- 不，谢谢.- 来吧, 伙计...
我的朋友...
想和些美女度过这个晚上吗？
什么?
一个美好的夜晚，加上几个美女.有兴趣吗?
就在这附近.
你想说什么?
进去, 喝杯东西, 看看周围...
就会有美女过来.
你如果想要更多, 你想做爱,那也是可以的, OK?
多少钱?
10欧元每杯饮料...
如果你不喜欢,你可以离开.
怎么样?这是在巴黎很好的一个纪念品.
相信我, 我不是骗子.
在那里?
晚上愉快.
- 晚上好.- 晚上好.
- Hi- 你叫什么名字?
我叫Simon.
- Sabrina, 很高兴认识你.- 一样.
你会请我喝杯饮料吗?
好的,但是要多少钱啊?
- 20欧元.- 20?
谢谢.
你从哪里来?
纽约.
- 纽约市...- 是的.
我说得不是很好, 英语.
我介绍一下我的朋友,对你来说有问题吗?
- 好的，可以.- Victoria, 过来这里.
- 这是我的朋友Victoria.- Hi.
你都准备好了? 没问题?
- 确定.- 好的，很好.
我去下洗手间再回来, OK?
- OK.- 拜.
- 谢谢.- 你想去后面房间吗?
- 多少钱?- 免费.
我们只坐在那里,就是这些.
- 嗯，好的.- 来吧.
你很帅
我不想告诉你这只是为了工作,我这么认为.
这很好. 谢谢.
看到这些女孩吗?
- Sabrina?- 和我聊天那个人...
这个女人，她不是需要钱，她是渴望钱!
今天她有3个客,而我只有一个.
一般来说, 这就是个交易, 懂?
如果她接了一个客人,那下一个就是我的..
然后下一个是她的,这是约定.
我对她就像姐妹那样. 我有吃的,就会和她分享.
她高兴了, 我会替她高兴.
但是对她来说，她不怎么分享.
- 对于我?我很需要这些钱.- 我明白.
所以你是来游览巴黎的?
是的。是的...
- 你有女朋友吗?- 没有.
你做什么的?
现在?没有.我刚毕业.
你看起来不太好.
我要近些看你.
我近视.
是吗?
我在大学研究眼睛.
- 真的?- 是的.
我研究眼睛和大脑的关系的.
- 你的法语很好.- 不，不是的.
- 是的，你说的很好.-我在高中学的, 可是很糟糕.
你要做爱吗?
多少钱?
如果你说150, 我会说 OK.
一些女生会说"就这个价钱",然后她们不会低于... 200.
和我, 我可以去到150.
- 150...?- 是的.
我给一半给我老板.如果我赚50,我会给她 25.
OK.
但是...
和你一起, 就不像是和那些胖子, 丑男人一起睡. 你知道?
和你,我会挺喜欢的.
我...
我把钱都花在酒吧了.我只有信用卡了
-你有信用卡?- 是的.
那也可以.把它给我.
OK.
谢谢.
Nadia?
对不起.
没关系.
我有个伤疤.
一条围巾?
不,伤疤. S-C-A-R... 'scar'.
这里.
- 没关系.- 我只是认为最后告诉你.
我喜欢事先告诉别人.
感觉怎样?
非常好.
我可以...
我可以看看你吗?
可以.
- 这就是那伤疤.- 没关系.
你可以转过去吗?
天哪!
噢，天哪!
操...
- 对不起.- 没关系.
我不想来
没关系.只要你高兴.
是的... 我很高兴.我很高兴.
谢谢.
你还好吗?
- 你呢?- 还好.
那是什么?
一个狐狸.我母亲给我的.
看.
这里.
- 很乱.- 不... 还好.
等下...
我要把它脱了.
脱了感觉好点.
记一下我的号码,你喜欢的话.
记一下我的号码,我们可以在外面见面.
同样价钱, 但是更好.
OK.
我想她.
'我知道,甜心.
'现在过得还可以.会变得更好的.'
是的.
你有和他聊天吗?
'Si?
'Si, 你可以看着我吗?
'喂? 喂!'
没有.我没和她说过话.
'我不明白.
如果你还想和她一起,
你应该打给她.'
唔.我不知道.
是的，我猜.
这对她不好.
'这很可笑.
'所有你对她所做的...
'听着，你还想和她在一起吗?'
我不知道.
'去找个法国女孩吧.
'找个意大利女孩.找个人.
'停止这样伤心.
'这不健康.'
'Si?'
我不是你女朋友,你可以告诉哦你要的是什么.
是吗?
好的.
- 说, "操我."- 操我.
说, "操我
操我.
'嘿，西蒙。我很高兴听到
" 你在旅行还有一切顺利"
'我犹豫是否要回你的信，因为我们分开的方式.
'我想我们最后还是分开一段时间,
'任何书信形式.
'我不知道你什么时候回来.
'但如果你回来了,请你尊重我还有我的生活.
事实是我不认为我了解你,或者说我根本不了解你.
'我不认为你了解我.
'我在前几个月意识到这些.
'我现在很幸福.
'最后一次我们见面,你吓到我了
'在你身边我不再感到舒适.
'希望你一切都好.Sincerely, Michelle.'
真的? 我想念一个派对?
不, 那个非常棒.我为我自己办的.
什么, 就像我不需要钱?
嘿,女孩们!
- 最近怎么样了?- 所以人都在这里了.
我们还能去什么地方?
要烟吗?
你为什么周围看?
你有毛病吗?
我在街上被攻击了.我可以进来吗?
谁打你了?
我...我被攻击了.那些人,他们拿走了我的东西.
哪里?
地铁站.
对不起.
你想我做什么?我在工作.
我...
你没有朋友吗?
不，我...
我只是需要些帮助
还有我不知道我能去什么地方.
我可以很你呆几分钟吗?
不，现在不行.
OK...
如果你想的画, 我们可以在2小时之后见面
在那个叫Le Café au Rendezvous那里.
左边, 角落了.
可以了吗?
你什么时候去那里?
下班之后.
两个小时之内.
OK.
- 你还好吗?- 是的，还可以.
你住在哪里?
我，我不....
你不知道你住哪里?
不...我应该要离开了.
- 什么?- 我应该今晚就离开的.
你现在没地方住了.
不.
不是现在.
好吧，那... 你愿意住在我的房子?
那样可以吗?
- 走吧. 我来付钱?- 是的，谢谢你.
坐在那里e.
- 你的房子很漂亮.- 我从一个老太太那里租的.
她有些孤独.
你的父母...
你不能向他们求助吗?
我不和我父母说话了.
但是我明天会想出些解决办法的.
谢谢.
操... 刺痛.
- 就这样?- 是的.
你还有其他伤口吗?
对不起, 什么?
哪里...
还有哪里疼?
我不知道.我不... 我不确定.
让我看看.
你想要什么?
我睡不着.
你可以和我聊多一会吗?
关于什么的?
我不知道.
任何东西.
Victoria是你的真名吗?
我的名字是Noura.
- Nora?- Noura...
Noura.
你在酒吧工作了多久?
几个月.
What did you do before?
我之前在巴黎外面的一间超市上班.
你从那里过来的?
是的.
我住在那里直到...
我离婚了.
你结过婚?
他很坏吗?
他神暴力.
他从不让我出去.
有一次，我醒了,在午夜的时候.
我怀孕了.
我有了个宝宝在我身体里.
我的肚子太大了.
我突然就醒了...
然后周围都是血.
我去到厨房.
我丈夫也在那里.他看着我.
我全身都是学,到处都是.
在我到医院之前...
他在厨房上了我.
你明白我刚才说的吗?
我认为是的,你有一个儿子.
谢谢你对我这么好.
'嘿，妈妈. 我在Prague,然后准备去Sarajevo.
'我很抱歉没和你联系,这里信号很差.
'我比之前感觉好很多,所以不用担心我
我遇见了某个人, 我认为你会喜欢她.
'她不是个婊子..
'当我回去的时候,我想重新思考
'不让你和父亲那样痛苦,总是围着房子闷闷不乐.
'我在这里感觉很好,这旅程值了.
'我认为你会惊讶我回去是会吸引多少焦点.
'我爱你. 想父亲问候.
'Love... your fox, Si.'
- 你在那里吗?- 是的.
- 嘿, 你怎么样了?- 难受的一天.
发生什么了?
我在旅馆见到一个客人.
很好强.
但是留给了我一些可乐.
要被酒吗？
好的.
你知道...
那晚我去酒吧然后说再见
我看到你和另外一些人在一起?
我知道我不应该这么想,
但这让我感到很奇怪.
这让你感到奇怪
我在工作.
你认为人们做事情只是因为喜欢
而不是因为需要去做?
你知道,这些人大部分...
如果他们撞车了,
我都不会在乎.
他们的老婆呢?
我的意思是, 你有没有想过他们的老婆?
不,我不是那样想的.
不...
我的意思是, 想一下, 因为...
这些人大部分都可能结婚了,是吗?
如果他们老婆知道你,然后...
她们会很不高兴.
- 这会摧毁他们的生活的.- 可能吧.
就拿今晚那个人来说.
他结婚了吗?
是的，他结了.
他有钱吗?
有.
OK, 想象一下.
你的手机... 没有照相机.
但是,如果有的话
你把它放这里.
你去坐那里.
无论发生什么事...
你都记下来了.
然后怎样?
然后...
然后...?
我的意思是,
与其从很多男人
身上的得到一点钱,
你可以从一个男人身上得到很多钱
这些人很好利用的.
你介意我换下音乐吗?
u，继续.
It was the one thing they didn't take.
When everybody leaves you lonely
And times are worse than sad
And the world is falling
on your head
Just remember, for all you know
Good or bad, come what may
You're gonna live tomorrow
If you don't die today
It takes a muscle to fall in love
It takes a muscle
to fall in love
It takes a muscle to fall in love
Now the fear got in me
Cutting me deep
That's where it's gonna stay
And never leave
Someone come and lay my worry
Someone come and kill...?
我睡不着.
你还好吗?
我在想那些家伙.
他们有妻子.
他们有钱.
我不知道他们住哪里,但是我有他们的号码.
OK.
那很好.
我们可以一起想办法.
我去拿电话.
看一下.
我帮你买了意见衬衫.
谢谢.
- 你喜欢蓝色吗?- 是的.
我喜欢海军蓝..
完美. 谢谢你.
试一下, 想这样.
等一下! 这样子不对.
There was a time when my world was filled with darkness
DDDarkness
And I stopped dreaming now I'm supposed to fill it up with something
Something, something
对不起，打扰一下.
你是Jean吗?
- 是的.- 你今晚见到一个女生吗?
什么?
你有Victoria的电话吗?请用你的邮箱发个邮件给她.
为什么?
我们有点东西给你看.
我们现在看吧.
不，不好意思.那不可能.
OK.我要书法语了,你能明白吗?
是的，我能明白.
我是个警察.
警察.
明白?
是的.
那意味这我可以,
如果我想...
我可以打爆你的头!
你明白吗?
是的.
如果我操了个妓女,关你什么事?
你真的的有东西,或者你在耍我?
如果是那样,我要揍你了.
明白?
对不起. 没事了.忘了它吧.
不!
停下来.
停.
想试下什么感觉吗?
你就是个累赘!
等下,我来告诉你.
转过去.
你喜欢那样吗?
- 是吗?- 是的.
像那样?
OK, 过来这里.
这样?
是的，很好.
- 快点?- Yeah...!
哦, 操.
操!
过来.
你还好吗?
- 是的，你呢?- 嗯.
我有没有告诉你我第一次见到一个女人在Boulevard?
我走去Boulevard.我母亲拉着我的手.
我们要去Sacré Coeur.那天是星期天.
那天...
我注意到一个女人在那栋建筑旁学习.
她很大.
她穿这件迷你裙,没有穿袜子.
她看着我.
她很漂亮.
然后用她的手指,像这样给我做了个动作.
她太近了, 我可以闻到她的味道了.
在那时候,我不知道那种味道是什么.
现在，我知道了.
性爱.
当我大了一点我去找她,
只是问他,"你想从我这里得到什么?"
明白吗?
"你想从一个8岁小孩身上得到什么?"
不穿衣服.
René?
是的.
你有Victoria的号码吗?
不好意思?
有些东西 Victoria想给你看.
请用你的邮箱给她发条信息.
为什么?
她才能给你送段视频过去.我才可以把东西留在你的邮箱.
等一下,等一下,等一下...
René?
你在开玩笑.
是吗?
- 你有文件给我吗?- 不，不是现在.
我赚那些钱不容易y.
我有老婆,孩子, 家庭
- 是的，我明白.- 我有责任在身上.
是的. 是的...这不是给我的.是给她的。
就这样?
不用闹大了.
- 我应该给你买双鞋子了.- 是的.
- 你要去Métro吗?- 为什么?
我正想从这里走过去.
- 是吗?- 是的.
- 这里?- 是的.附近有家商店.
- 稍后见... OK?- OK.
- Bye.- Bye, 甜心.
- Bye.- Bye.
你确定你的感觉吗?
看这我的眼睛.
所以?
这就足够了. 想要被饮料吗?
可乐.
你又从这里经过了...
- 希望是.- 你不会忘记我们吧?
当然不会.
你留在巴黎吗, 我想?
不，不，我要离开了.
不, 一天一次.
爱情稍纵即逝.
不管什么,我现在感觉好多了.
为爱情干杯!
我也可以找到爱情吗!
嘿!
你还...记得我吗?
是的! 是的,我记得你.
是的, Simon.你是...
Marianne.
你住这附近?
是的..
你呢?
-是的...- 我还以为你离开巴黎了.
我准备离开,但我很喜欢这里
所以我打算待久一点.
还有... 你住哪里?
我在附近的旅馆.
看k.我现在要去见人了,我怎么联系你?
- 你要我的号码?-是的.
- 你有纸吗?- 有.
看.
这是你的过错.
是你做这些的.
我做了什么?
- 什么?- 他没有接受那些钱.
OK.
我可以帮你拿什么?
这里, 我有些东西给你.
当我还是个小孩的时候
我妈妈给了我这个东西
因为她说,我让她想起一个小狐狸。
我...我经常想成为一只老虎.
是吗?
我经常认为自己更像一只狮子.
你在研究什么?
法国文学.
- 是吗?- 是的.
OK. 那个时期的?
中世纪的还有文艺复兴.
你是学什么的?
我毕业了,这年的早些时候.
但是我是学神经系统学的.
我是研究眼睛和大脑的关系的.
我的这些项目是关于周围视觉的.
它是通过 'crowding'和 'size pooling'来处理的.
一个物体有多宽是由周围物体加权平均决定的.
它叫做'size pooling'.
无论怎样, 很无聊, 我知道.
但是它被出版了, 实际上.
你现在在巴黎做什么?
实话实说?
是的.
没事情做. 我...
我来这里有段时间没事情做.
OK.
- 你介意我问你些东西吗?- 不.
我很好奇...
你的眼睛...为什么会这样移动.
是的...
从我父亲那里遗传的.
这叫做"眼球震颤."
- 眼球震颤.- 是的.
OK. 我不知道在英语里面叫什么.
是的.
对不起. 我不是想让你尴尬. 这很...
很迷人,实际上.
谢谢. 我很好.
我的意思是.这很好看.
谢谢.
- Simon?- 是的.
你在哪里?
我在帮我们买食物.
W你为什么出去那么久?
是的，我...我感到很抱歉.
我去散步了.
你还好吗?
听着. 明天,我需要些钱
因为我需要给你买些东西.
你在做什么?
和我做爱.
Oh, no, no, no, no...
'René.毕一声后给我留下信息.'
嘿, René, 又是我.
停着. 我也不想这么快打给你, 但是...
我们要谈谈更多的钱.
我会一直打给你知道我找到你. 还有, OK...
谢谢, 再见.
'René. 留下...'
René. 在毕一声后留下信息.
René, 当我打给你的时候拿起你的手机.
Walking up to me expecting
Walking up to me expecting words
It happens all the time
Present company accepted
Present company except the worst
It happens every night
Present company
excluded in every way
Makes me wanna stay
Killing it with close inspection
Killing it can only make it worse
It sort of makes it breed
Present company accepting
Presently we all expect the worst
Works just like a need
Present company
Included in the fight
Don't you want me to wake up?
Then give me just a bit of your...?
我可以看这你吗?
- 可以.- 是吗?
我不喜欢这样.
- 什么?- 你看我的方式.
为什么?你很漂亮.
来这里.
- 你饿吗?- 是的.
- 我们该去哪里?- Montmartre.
天哪... 对不起.
他是谁
只是我的...我一起住的表兄.
什么?
不...我以为你住在旅馆的.
什么t?
是的,你这样告诉我的.
不... 我刚来的时候住旅馆. 现在我和表兄住了.
但是他一直打给我...
还有, 以防是重要的事情,我应该和他说话.
可以帮我付下帐吗,帮我点多被咖啡?
- 好的.- 谢谢.
嘿...一切好吗?
你昨晚为什么不回家?'
我... 我知道.
在外面过夜很抱歉.
'你和谁一起?'
一个朋友.
'什么朋友?'
听着. 我现在不能说,但是不用担心.我很快回去.
- 你还好吗?- 是的.
我的父母,他们很担心我.
他们一直打给我表兄.
我一星期没和他们说话了.
-但是你父母离婚了.- 什么?
你告诉我你父母离婚了.
是的, 他们离婚了.我意思是,我母亲和我继父.
但是我母亲重婚了.我有一个继父.
等一下.
- 你好, René?- '不.谁?'
- 对不起.你死、是谁?- 'Mathilde.
'你之前有打过René'的电话吗?'
我... 是的, 我可以和René谈话吗?
'不, 你不能和René谈话.'
- 抱歉, 你说什么?- René'死了.
'告诉我你为什么打René'的电话这么多次.'
听着,现在我过得不好.可以叫René打给我吗?
现在不行,先生!
对不起. 这家伙...天哪!
你还好吗?
是的, 我很好.我只是今天不好.
和你喝咖啡很有趣!
什么?
只是开玩笑.
- 什么意思?- 没有! 只是开玩笑.
天哪!
你知道上呢么,对不起. 我...
-如果你要走的话, 走吧.- 我...
我没钱了.我到时候还你?
好的.
我很高兴.
OK, 我会打给你的.
抱歉.
我今天有个电话
来自一个女人.
然后我认为我们要跑了e.
你昨晚去哪里了?
你为什么不回家?
我告诉你了.
我出去了.
听着
我们要尽快走.
你让我很反感.
你听到我说什么了吗?我们要走了.
滚出去.
你就是一坨屎.
你还说谎.
- 你说法语的时候我听不懂.- 你个骗子.
好吧.
我走了.
很好,走吧.你真让人可怜.
拿上你的钱.
拿着.
我不需要你的钱.
看看你自己, 看...
你是一个懦夫.
你不是一个男人.
你知道的,我们得到我们应得的.
你在说什么?
我为你做这些.你可以为了你儿子花这些钱.
我从不要求你什么, Simon.
我只是在做我认为合适的.
我要打电话了.
什么?
你听到的.
你打给谁?
- 你做了什么?- 我打给她!
哦, 你他妈的.
你他妈的.
我爱你.
我爱你. 是的. 我爱你.
你疯了.
你这个恶心的人.
你很恶心!
婊子!
把你的手放下!
操.
- 嘿.- Hi.
很抱歉, 我很冷.
我在外面等着某人让我进去.
- 刚才对不起了.- 没关系.
你还好吗?
不, 我...
我感觉不好.
很对不起, 我...
我没地方去了.我只是来看你的.
你认为我还能和你待多一天吗?
你要进来坐吗?
我... 很抱歉打扰你们.
我想待多几天,知道我解决...
还要去哪里.
是的,我...
很抱歉, 我不能帮你.
你不能留在这里.
- OK...- 对不起...
生日快乐
祝你生日快乐...
生日快乐, Carlo
祝你生日快乐
谢谢你们!
哦,干.
Carlo,有个人要见你.
你在这里做什么?
很抱歉打扰你们, 但是t、...
我不知道谁会在这里.我是过来拿我的行李的.
- 你还好吗- 是的
我遇到了一个女孩.我旅行有一段时间了.
- 那很好.- 是的.
这是我的生日，所以这有些我的朋友...
- 生日快乐.- 谢谢.
让我来给你介绍.这是我母亲朋友的儿子.
也是我的美国表亲.
- Hi.- Hi.
要喝一杯吗?
你介意我洗个澡吗?
不，随便吧.
打扰了.
- 有一个美好的晚上.- 你也是.
我让他住在这里几天...
他不会长住的.
'您的电话已转发给自动语音信息系统'
'Hi, 你到了Mary那里就给我打电话.'
妈妈?
妈妈...
妈妈!
'Michelle...
'过去几个月我花了很多时间
'在思考我们的关系p.
我从没有哭过那么多.
'我知道我们都需要成长, 尤其是我,
'需要我们分开一段时间.
'我开始变得很依赖你.
'情感上甚至是经济上,
'有些东西我从没有想过.
'我知道我那是的行为让气氛变得更加恶化.
'我有很的爱想去表达,还有我知道我要成为什么人.
'那种会让我父亲自豪的人.
'那5年我没有迷失
'一个我最要好的女生成为了我的伴侣.
'我的生活有了爱,但是现在没有了，这几乎杀了我.'
- 不, 请出示你的护照.- 神?
从你钱包拿出护照.
OK.
你在巴黎做了什么?
我去度假的.
你做什么的?
- 抱歉?- 你做什么的?
- 你做什么工作的?- 我是个学生, 但是我毕业了.
你学什么的?
法国文学.
你知道你呆在这里超过90天了吗.
不, 我...
对不起.我没意识到.
等一下
'无论之前发生什么,我不危险.
'我不会伤害你的.
'我知道我需要时间去成长.
'还有我知道你也需要时间.
'希望我们不久后可以见面,
'像我们所知道的那些人...
'希望我们不久后可以见面,像我们所知道的那些人...
'希望我们不久后可以见面
'像我们所知道的那些人然后我们会成为那样的人,
'在12街的角落还有大学里,
我们会在最初接吻的地方接吻.然后重新开始
'对不起,我很快会见到你的.
'Love always. Simon. Your lion.'
好了. 你可以走了.
继续吧.
谢谢，再见.